this is nice though i'm getting older
it's a young guy a couple of young
people like you in the middle you don't
know what i'm going to talk about a
minute
you're not going to understand
i'm getting older you'll get it
sorry
this happened last tuesday i woke up my
knee swollen and was killing me
the whole day i spent thinking about
what i possibly could have done the day
before
because i am extremely inactive so how
did that happen
with the cvs how to get a wrap all the
like knee wraps showed where you can
still be active like every knee rap was
like you could play basketball today you
can work i'm like i'm not gonna need
that kind of rap um
i'm gonna need to be able to sit and
relax as i watch tv do you have that
wrap
[Laughter]
i went to bed that night woke up the
next morning my knee was fine
like it never even hurt my shoulder shot
couldn't even feel my shoulder
i don't know what's happening to my body
but as you're old you can't run to the
doctor every time something twitches
you'll be there every day
the only time i go to the doctor
nowadays when two things are messed up
at the same time i'm saying like if i'm
coughing and limping at the same time
then i go it's like
why okay why
why is that moving
i gotta get that looked at
i've been going to the same like year
like over my life span i've gone to
three different doctors my pediatrician
till i was 15. then from 15 to 22 i was
going to a doctor every time he would
diagnose me he would give me the same
diagnosis swollen glands no matter what
i gained with i'm like
okay i just want to glance like did you
i think it's pneumonia you want to get a
better look
he was giving me a physical once he felt
right he was oh there's a swollen gland
i'm like there
there's a gland there
okay
last time i went to him i had a like
knot right here just like right here
like this weird knot in my groin
and i was 22 very scared you know what i
mean like please
get in here with it with some mirrors
and lights and find out why
that's there right now he was like oh
right here oh it's a swallowing clan i'm
like is that the last chapter you read
so i stopped going to the doctor until i
was in my 40s now my doctor's only
diagnosis for me is you got to lose
weight every time
you gotta lose weight i'm like are you
trying to fight me because i will punch
you in your face
and have you check my glands how am i
glanced
what is this like a big giant gland you
don't even know
why don't you read my chart do you even
know your patience
i was out of town once i went to like i
had to go to one of those little you
know those like ready-made like urgent
care dog not like a real doctor it's
like a strip mall doctor
it's a pizzeria dollar store emergency
facility
laundromat
i've never been there ever i'm sitting
in his office he comes in the room he's
like wow you look horrible
you don't know me
this could be my everyday face
i could be here for my ankle you big
jerk
just made me so uncomfortable when i got
back home i made an appointment to see
my doctor i'm like can you do some blood
work find out why i look so sick to
strangers
because we're gonna do some blood work
you guys you also need an ultrasound
and ultrasound how fat am i
am i pregnant
it doesn't work like that
he sent me for an ultrasound i was so i
don't like here's one of my things i
don't like taking my shoulder in front
of people i'm very uncomfortable with my
body i'm fat i'm white i'm very shiny
i don't like it
i was just hoping there was old people
like an old doctor but it was two
beautiful girls running the machine i
had to take my shirt off and there i am
you know what i look like do you ever go
to a pizzeria and you see like the blob
of dough
like the big blob of dough and then they
make little balls and make a little
pizza ball that's what i look like i
look like someone's getting ready to
come in and pop out little pizza balls
i'm just laying there fat everywhere
just
and she takes this jelly
i felt like she was
basting a turkey
i felt so much shame that day
go back to my doctor he goes yeah your
ultrasound was fine but you do have a
fatty liver
why would i not
so my body's tapping my liver is just
beautiful shredded
goes to the gym every day ripped
beautiful
beautiful ripped liver
a week later he calls you bags like mike
your cholesterol and sugar are very high
you got to cut back on carbs you got to
kind of quit candy and he just said it
like
quicker it's like death
i mean like he didn't tell me to get my
family in like nothing i mean like
like let's bring this is some serious
news i'm getting ready to drop on you
just you told me i can never have
another you know peanut butter cup you
don't think my mom should be here to
hold me right now
[Laughter]
he's like well i need you to quit candy
i'm like well i'm not gonna so what else
can i do
he said don't you want to see your
children grow up maybe have
grandchildren absolutely but i also want
a reese's peanut butter cups
back to the lab invent a pill
you think i'm quitting
peanut butter cups for grandchildren
i'm not going to put candy for my kids
that are actually alive
you want me to give them up for a couple
of maybe kids
hypothetical children no i don't think
what if they're jerks what if i don't
like them
now i have a resentment because i quit
candy it's not worth it
it's not worth it
[Music]
you